guys and girls and guys I bring you
chavales y chavalas y chavales os traigo
another excerpt or rather another
otro extracto o sea otro extracto de
video excerpt in which we're going to talk about auro
vídeo en el que vamos a hablar de auro
play ok I
play ok
know you're burning in my kids
sé que estáis ardiendo en mi chavalería
dot com I know you're full on with this
puntocom sé que estáis a full con este
topic
tema
and look something happened something happened in a
y mira ha pasado ha pasado algo en un
live stream that I thought was wonderful and I'm
directo que me ha parecido maravilloso y
bringing it here to comment on it I know that this thing
lo traigo aquí para comentarlo ya sé que
here of releasing videos every
esto aquí de sacar a vídeo todos los
day from now on a play seems a bit like the
días de ahora un play parece un poco el
secondary channel of being here okay but it has to be
canal secundario de estar aquí vale pero
mentioned because it seemed
hay que comentarlo porque me ha parecido
very nice to me it turns out that aurum play
muy bonito resulta ser que aurum play le
makes a video reading the cards okay he
hace un vídeo leyendo las cartas vale le
makes a video reading the cards like
hace un vídeo leyendo las cartas como
maps to me on many more occasions he read
mapas a mí en muchas ocasiones más leyó
the card we have reacted no what is it
la carta hemos reaccionado no qué es lo
with this what that
que pasa con esto qué
many times even if I don't believe in this thing
que muchas veces aunque no crea en esto
about cards and all that they start to
de las cartas y demás te empiezan a
tell you things that you feel identified with
decir cosas que te sientes identificado
so I think that
entonces yo creo que
now a play when he opened this video
ahora un play cuando abrió este vídeo
although he had seen it before he also
aunque lo había visto antes también lo
wanted to react to it in his live stream
ha querido reaccionar en su directo
because he has been able to feel identified
porque se ha podido sentir identificado
with some things okay let's see
con algunas cosillas vale vamos a ver yo
I have pointed out here the two things that I
yo he señalado aquí las dos cosas que me
liked for  watch it here live
han gustado para verla aquí en directo
but you can watch the entire video it's
pero podéis ver el vídeo entero está por
uploaded eight hundred thousand times so you
ahí subido de ochocientas mil veces para
feel like you're going to be in a position
sentirte que vas a estar en una posición
where everyone around you is
donde todas las personas a tu alrededor
going to have something to say or something to give their
van a tener algo que decir o algo que
opinion
opinar
and it seems like this has to do with
y parece que esto tiene que ver con
someone in your life there's
alguien en tu vida
going to be pressure
va a haber presión
around you that is going to
a tu alrededor que va a afectar
directly affect a person in your life
directamente a una persona en tu vida
and it's as if to a certain extent you didn't
y es como si hasta cierto punto tú no
want this person who is
quisieras que esta persona que es
important to you during this year 2021 to
importante para ti durante este año 2021
receive this impact they will receive this
recibiera este impacto recibirá esta
pressure from the people who listen to you
presión por parte de las personas que te
because you feel that this could push
porque sientes que esto podría alejar a
this person away from you
esta persona de ti
present is that this energy of putting
presenta es que esta energía de poner a
this person like in
esta persona como en
this could even be also
esto incluso podría ser también hasta
something that you have very much
algo que tú tienes muy
like a fear
como un temor
and your fear is exposing someone in your
y tu temor es exponer a alguien en tu
private life to your personal life to
vida privada a tu vida personal a la
public opinion
opinión pública
because of the criticism that they could be
por las críticas que podría estar
receiving and thinking that this could
recibiendo y por pensar de que eso pudo
have or could push that person away from
haber o podría alejar a esa persona de
your life
tu vida
and of course you are listening to what they
y por supuesto está escuchando lo que
are saying or in other words, on a little platform
está diciendo o sea a un estradito que
below you
hay abajo
are seeing that maybe they are going to see themselves
le estáis viendo que tal vez se va a ver
in a situation in their life in  the one who
en una situación en su vida en la que se
had involved an important person in her life
había involucrado una persona de su vida
not that other people in her
importante no que otras personas de su
life are also involved everyone is
vida también sea la involucrada todos
going to have something to say and auro is going
van a tener algo que decir y auro se va
to feel obligated perhaps to
a ver en la obligación tal vez de
expose someone that he doesn't want to expose
exponer a alguien que no quiere exponer
because they're going to kill him if they put him or
porque se lo van a cargar si lo ponen o
something like that okay
algo así vale
decreed only
decretó solamente
with those and desired no no no it's not
con esas y deseado
me it's the video that is
no no no soy yo es el vídeo que está
muted okay but well where do you
silenciado vale pero bueno por dónde
think the shots can go
creéis ustedes que pueden ir los tiros
where do you think you can
por donde creen ustedes que pueden
train yourselves to do thank you very much
entrenarse de hacer muchas gracias
because this person surely what he has
porque esta persona seguramente lo que
done has been seen a few
haya hecho ha sido verse unos cuantos de
videos of salt he became a man he will have
vídeo de sal se hizo hombre se habrá
seen a few videos it's the entourage he will
visto unos cuantos vídeos es al séquito
have been informed of the move and there will be
se habrá informado de la movida y habrá
catches not very difficult to catch him and
pillas tampoco muy difícil pillar el y
global but let's get to the part that I
globales pero vamos a la parte que me
like it
gusta
doesn't let me you to send you a super chat
no me deja you to mandarte un super chat
of five euros
de cinco euros
to blair acz because they don't want you to
para blair acz porque no quieren que te
spend a lot youtube look for you and doesn't
gastes mucho youtube mira por ti y no
want you to spend a lot
quiere que te gastes mucho
a proposal of
una propuesta de
the marriage proposal by the
la propuesta de matrimonio por la carta
three of cups card
del tres de copas
a union
una unión
on the part of
de parte de
your partner receiving this pressure or rather
que tu pareja reciba esta presión o sea
I love it because this kid what
me encanta porque este chaval lo que ha
he has done  tarot readers I see all the
hecho él tarotistas yo verse todos los
videos dirty things from us
vídeos desaseos desde nosotros
Michelle welcome I don't even know how many
michelle bienvenido no sé ni cuántos
members we have today let's see I
miembros llevamos hoy a ver
don't even know how many members we have today
no sé ni cuántos miembros llevamos hoy
but well we have reached 1531
pero bueno hemos llegado a 1531
1531 members you are crazy
1531 miembros estáis loquísimo
this is what we wanted to do one member we are
esta es lo quisimos hacer un miembro
going to reach 1600 today we are going to reach
vamos a llegar a 1600 hoy vamos a llegar
1600 what
a 1600
could cause
que podrían ocasionar
well this does not have to be 2021 we
bueno esto no hace falta que sea 2021
already did this
esto ya lo hemos
in 2020 I tell you now that I know it
en el 2020 ya te digo ahora que sé
sounds very bad let's see I'm
se escucha muy mal a ver
going to look for it on twitter because I have
voy a buscarlo en twitter que en twitter
seen it on twitter I'm going to look for it quickly
lo he visto voy a buscarlo rápidamente
on twitter and on twitter it will be with more
en twitter y en twitter estará con más
with more sounds I don't know why this
con más sonidos no sé por qué esta
person has censored some part of the
persona ha censurado alguna parte del
audio I don't know what
audio no sé qué
but on twitter I have seen it and if I'm
pero en twitter sí que lo he visto y si
not mistaken here here here here it
no me equivoco por aquí por aquí por
is the first but well here here it
es la primera pero bueno he aquí aquí ya
is the first but well obviously
es la primera pero bueno evidentemente
if this has to talk about someone it
esto si tiene que hablar de alguien
talks about begin that is to say sara since she has
habla de begin es decir sara desde que
become known
se ha hecho conocida
all the ass sniffers have come out to touch
han salido todos los huele culos a tocar
them  eggs
los huevos
that's obvious there are people who have become
eso es evidente hay gente que ha sido
famous and the
hacerse famosa y salir los cuatro
usual four miserable people come out to say
miserables de siempre a decir
look at what tweets they had from the year
es que mirar qué tweets tenía del año
2000 the usual four miserable people are already
2000 ya están los cuatro miserables de
annoying you and if I
siempre a tocar los huevos y si yo lo
interpreted it like that and the truth is that they
interpretó así y la verdad es que lo
nailed it people who well as long as you are not
clava gente que bueno mientras no eres
known nothing happens you are not of interest to
conocido no pasa nada no le interesas a
anyone you
nadie
know but when you become known
sabes pero a la que te haces conocido la
people's envy
envidia de la gente
rises and they attack let's see look at her I
sube y atacan a ver mírala
understand that when a person does
yo entiendo que cuando una persona
not succeed or is not a public person
no triunfa no o no es personal público
our booming or whatever you want to call it
nuestra en auge o como queráis llamarlo
do not criticize them too much and do not release their
no las critiquen mucho y no saque sus
things their stirrer their moves and so on
cosas su remover sus movidas y demás
okay and that when that person hits the
vale y que cuando esa persona pega un
fan and is on everyone's lips is
boom y está en boca de todo el mundo es
when things come out I can understand
cuando sale la cosa lo puede entender
but
pero
that they released it just when sara
que lo hayan sacado justo cuando sara
is pushing it in tweets
lo está apretando en tweets
when she was not an
cuando ella no es que fuera una persona
anonymous person until now, I
anónima hasta el momento
mean she
o sea ella
was already aurum play's girlfriend she
ya era la novia de aurum play
danced very much I mean it has always been
bailaba muchísimas gracias o sea siempre
known that there will be a play had
se ha conocido que habrá un play tenía
iker's girlfriend sara juan welcome hey
la novia de iker a sara juan bienvenido
funny  guys come on let's do
oye gracia chavales vamos vamos a hacer
look there are four thousand and something people
mira hay cuatro mil y pico de personas
right now it's worth
ahora mismo vale
the opposite of the minimum possible price
lo opuesto al mínimo de precio posible
the one who doesn't do it is because they don't want to it
el que no se haga es porque no quiera
would be great and it would be a disappointment for
sería la [__] y sería un disgusto para
some people if we reached 1,600
algunas personas que llegásemos a 1.600
members with this live I'll leave it there and
miembros con este directo ahí lo dejo y
also when I finish this live I'm
además cuando termine este directo estoy
in Jan
en jaén
I'm with a hi who loves to talk or
estoy con un hi que flipa hablar o
use when I finish by when I finish
utilizar al terminar por cuando termine
this live I'm going to watch the second
este directo voy a ver el segundo
episode I don't know if more I think there are two
capítulo no sé si más creo que hay dos
branches of 'physics or chemistry' 'the
ramas de 'física o química' 'el
reunion' I do
reencuentro'
n't know if you like it I'm not as much of a woman as
no sé si os gusta no soy tan mujer como
I am well yes there will be women here
yo bueno si aquí habrá gente mujer
too then I physics or chemistry was
también entonces yo física o química fue
my series of my favorite series when they
mi serie de mi serie favorita cuando la
kicked it off and now they've released the
echaron y ahora es han sacado el
reunion so I'm going to watch the
reencuentro entonces voy a ver el
second episode which was today starting at
segundo capítulo que era hoy a partir de
12 okay because they could have already
las 12 vale porque ya podrían haberle
released all this [ __ ] from Sara no
sacado a sara toda la [__] esta no
all the [ __ ] this is from
a toda la [__] esta es a la de los
your old ones what splashes them euro
tuyos antiguos lo que les salpica euro
lawsuit in all the time that she has had
pleito en todo el tiempo que ha tenido
fame euro enplater all this life
fama a euro enplater toda esta vida
because  they haven't had time to do it something else thank you
porque no han tenido tiempo a hacerlo
very much welcome they
otra vaina muchas gracias bienvenido
could have done it but nevertheless they have
podrían haberlo hecho pero sin embargo
n't
no lo ha hecho no lo han hecho hasta
done it they haven't done it until now you know what my theory is everyone everyone we know that people on twitter and that aura will use the see light I don't know who doesn't count and a lot of people were very heavy very hooligan I didn't say I didn't in the years
hooligan no decía yo no en los años de
89 years ago okay what I've done on
hace 89 años vale que he hecho en
twitter it was yes walesa I
twitter era si walesa
saw that they imposed the stupidity worse to be
vi que imponían la burrada peor para ser
funnier but the thing they
más graciosos pero la cosa
don't put anything nobody has taken the
no ponen nada nadie se ha tomado los
hype welcome
había bombo bienvenido
direct here many months ago
directo aquí hace muchos meses
commenting on something I said yes yes yes it's that
comentando alguna cosa he dicho sí sí sí
this one found out about things it didn't
es que ésta se enteró de las cosas no
say it was a dog it didn't get up and in
ponía era un perro no se levantó y de
fact there's one thing that nobody is
hecho hay una cosa que nadie está
saying and the way of the site now I
diciendo y la vía del sitio ahora me
love the workers taking this out and I
encantan las obreras sacando esto y me
love everyone who is
encanta todo el mundo que está
criticizing fact
criticando hecho
but they don't realize to say a
pero no caen en la cuenta de decir una
little thing they don't realize to say a
cosita no caen en la cuenta decir una
little thing that I'm going to say
cosita que la voy a decir yo
that the vast majority of people that you're
que la gran mayoría de gente que estás
putting up until now with this [ __ ]
poniendo hasta ahora con estas [__]
defend the
defiende
group that  we already know you
al grupo que ya sabemos
know what that
sabéis qué
if maybe these people had
que si tal vez esta gente tenía en tuit
unfortunate tweets at the time like that but
desafortunados en la época así pero
you know that Ingrid's at that
sabéis que los de ingrid en aquella
time were also unfortunate because
época también eran desafortunados porque
Ingrid belonged to the English group and
ingrid pertenecía al grupo inglés y
also participated in all these
también participaba en todas estas
things because nobody takes out Ingrid's tweets
movidas porque nadie saca los tweets de
what things nobody has realized this no, they
qué cosas nadie ha caído el eso no
are not telling us anything about Ingrid they
a ingrid nos están diciendo nada
are not taking out her tweets
no están sacando sus tweets
which were also gems
que también eran joyas
well I sincerely this apart from
bueno yo sinceramente esto aparte de que
looking through the force it was everyday it
mire por la force era de cotidiano
is clear I already put them in my video no
está claro ya les puse en mi vídeo no
this has also been motivated by
esto también lo ha motivado el hermano
Auron's brother from the tweets I'm going to drop
de auron desde los tweets voy a soltar
this bomb this person has such if I
esta bomba esta persona tiene tal si yo
said this if they direct the other having
dijera esto si dirigen al otro al haber
stirred it has been that it has been as a result of
removido ha hecho que ha sido a raíz de
Beijing doing the live shows well everything has
que beijing haga los directos pues todo
been a snowball that has
ha sido una bola de nieve que se ha
become bigger okay that's been like this since
hecho más grande vale eso es así desde
always I mean right now well
siempre es decir sea ahora mismo bueno
in fact it has even happened to Paul to Paul
de hecho le ha pasado hasta paul a paul
there are people on twitter who when he became
hay gente en twitter que al hacerse
famous they started to take out tweets from the
conocido le empezaron a sacar tweets del
year 2012 that were plan that a long time ago
año 2012 que eran plan que hace tiempo
because they are going to force spy aso that you are like
porque van a forzar a spy aso que estás
this but at the moment
así pero al momento
what are you doing clown javi I am not going to
qué estás haciendo payaso javi no te voy
let you more accounts x as always
a dejar más cuentas x de siempre igual
the truth is that I do not have it you
la verdad es que no lo tengo
have another account
tienes otra cuenta
alba but I do not work for you I am not going to
yo alba pero no te labor no te la voy a
ask you for it because fears have a remedy
pedir porque los miedos tiene remedio
or I mean I managed an account to the glass a
o sea manejaba una cuenta al vaso una
friend okay she is a follower of mine for a
amiga vale es una seguidora mía ya hace
long time and a friend invades an
mucho tiempo y amiga le invade a una
account but it was not because of the issue of
cuenta pero no era por lo del tema de
helping or anyone you know it was not because of
ayudar ni por nadie sabes no era por
something you I cannot explain because it is
algo de usted no puedo explicar porque
not something on the internet okay it was not because of
no es algo de internet vale no era por
something that you knew and every time she
una cosa que ustedes supieran y siempre
leaves me an account I mess it up
que me deja una cuenta la lío
every time she leaves me the account it
siempre que me deja la cuenta
is that I am a pubescent guy I have no
es que soy un púber tío no tengo no
excuse Alba I have no excuses I do not know I am
tengo excusa alba no tengo excusas no sé
not going to tell you side because I have no
no voy a decirte lado porque no tengo
excuses sorry sorry for bothering you with your
excusas perdón perdón por jorobar te tus
gossip okay well she is angry girl
cotilleos vale pues tiene ira chavala
her things there are for her gossip and
sus cosillas hay para sus cotilleos y
everything she just bothered okay everyone
todo solo jorobó vale todos los
sacrifices them for me but well
sacrifican por mí pero bueno
anyway kids let's try
igualmente chavales vamos a intentarlo
okay and let's try to reach
vale y vamos a intentar llegar a los mil
1,600 members okay because  everyone has
600 miembros vale porque a todos han
said welcome except me
dicho bienvenido menos a mí
Cristian welcome offerings
cristian bienvenidos de ofrendas
don't be offended Cristian welcome
no te ofendas cristian bienvenidos
Javi send me a greeting it makes me
javi mándame un saludo que me hace
happy you that I have a lollipop lollipop
ilusión te que me piruleta piruleta
a greeting corp
un saludo corp
e I
e
mean you are anonymous it's okay
es decir tú eres anónimo no pasa nada
you can do whatever you want nobody
puedes hacer lo que quieras a nadie le
cares javi as it is very well you are not
importa javi como está muy bien no eres
interesting they are not going to gain popularity
interesante no van a ganar popularidad
thanks to a nobody so to speak
gracias a un don nadie por así decirlo
but when you become famous
pero a la que te hace el famoso salen
the usual opportunists come out to annoy the
los oportunistas de siempre a tocar los
internet vigilantes
huevos los justicieros de internet
and that is what this man is saying
y eso es lo que está contando este
and he is absolutely right and this
hombre y tiene toda la razón del mundo y
is the case with Sara from the moment that
es el caso de sara desde el momento en
Sara became a little more well
el que sara se hizo un poquito más
known thanks to mangas the strips
conocida gracias a mangas los strips
etcetera the ones that came out could have come
etcétera salieron los de que podrían
out ten years ago but not
haber salido hace diez años pero no
now is the time now that she is
ahora es el momento ahora que es
known to win there are some earrings or
conocida para ganar hay unos aretes o
win anything right well some
ganar cualquier cosa verdad bueno alguna
people to win okay well normal when
gente por ganar vale pues normal cuando
someone is on the rise it is normal that people
alguien está en auge es normal que se
talk about that person it is logical and the
hable de esa persona es lógico y a la
people who don't like it then
gente que le caiga mal pues luego que
speak badly and bad things come out but there are
hable mal y salió cosas malas pero hay
people  that he doesn't do it to gain anything in
gente que no lo hace por ganar nada a
return there are people who do it simply
cambio hay gente que lo hace simplemente
to screw because they are happy screwing
por [__] porque son felices jodiendo a
people
la gente
okay
vale
or people with no life boring people and
o la gente sin vida gente aburrida y
sad people and that's it and the right thing very
gente triste y ya está y lo acertado muy
well let's see I'm not afraid at all the
bien a ver yo no tengo ningún miedo la
truth he says that I'm afraid afraid it's not to
verdad él dice que tengo miedo miedo no
say I feel bad because that
es decir me sabe mal
she had a bad time etcetera but I'm
pues que ella lo pasé mal etcétera pero
not afraid because they can come
miedo no tengo porque pueden venir de
one by one he doesn't have to be afraid
uno en uno no tiene que tener miedo
at all because now he doesn't have he has
ninguno porque ahora no tiene
ways with which to defend himself very
tiene formas con las que defenderse muy
well and now he is employed besides he is a
bien y ahora emplea además es una
person that everyone appreciates he has
persona que todo el mundo aprecia él se
worked hard and now a play moves a
lo ha currado y ahora un play mueve un
finger and we trust him okay and if he
dedo y confiamos en él vale y si él
wanted to counterattack he would hire
quisiera contraatacar contrataría
counterattack and endorse the things that there is no
contraatacar y avale las cosas que no
fear if he does not feel comfortable although he did
hay miedo si no se siente cómodo aunque
not like to go through this no
no le gustaba pasar por este trago no
that it is not a circumstance that
que no es una circunstancia que él le
bothers him okay have you already imagined the depor if he
mole vale se ha imaginado ya el depor si
tries our involved in controversy
intenta nuestras metido en polémica
a bird gets it without wanting to
a un ave se lo mete sin que quiera
get involved but already in itself he does not
meterse pero ya ya de por si a él no le
like being involved in controversy and in the
gusta estar metido en polémica y en la
last week he was involved in controversy
última semana estaba metido en polémica
and on top of that with  a topic as personal as
y encima con un tema tan personal como
with people whose
con gente que su familia de primera de
first-class family, let's not say one that I eat them
primer rango no digamos no uno que me
all can see it's
los como a todos pueden ver
not for Dallas as it does for Dallas
no es por dallas como lo hace por dallas
and I would count I'm [ __ ] great let's see
y yo contara estoy de [__] madre a ver
what about the account that Alba left me is
lo de la cuenta que me ha dejado alba es
because there is a is that they are not going to
porque hay un es que no lo van a
understand dude they are related to the
entender tío están relacionadas con las
moves made by the people who
movidas hechas de la gente que me
report my twitter account of
reporta la cuenta de twitter de dni
false IDs and things from such haters hater who
falsos y cosas de tal haters hater que
are sick okay then what happens is that
están enfermos vale entonces lo que pasa
those sick people start
que esos enfermitos pues se ponen a
saying stupid things and more about me donkey disi
decir burradas y más de mí burra disi
more about me and I wanted to report them okay what happened why did
más de mí y he querido reportar les vale
Alva have an account with which I could
alva tenía una cuenta con la que podía
see them
verlos
because they have me blocked from
porque me tienen bloqueado de todas
everywhere so that I can't report them
partes para que yo no les pueda reportar
or see the things they post and apart from the fact that they
ni ve las cosas que ponen y aparte de
post valuable personal things they
que ponen cosas personales valiosas
post personal things like and even
ponen cosas personales en plan e incluso
personal data okay then they have
datos personales vale entonces me ha
stopped trying to deal with the account, I have not
dejado de tratar de la cuenta no me ha
even had time to see it Alva and log in
dado tiempo ni a verla alva e iniciar
from Chrome okay because I can't log in
sesión desde el chrome vale porque no lo
from my mobile or
puedo iniciar sesión desde el móvil ni
nothing
nada
and suddenly the bull took over and I
y de repente me acogió el toro y de
started directly preparing kilos and I didn't
empezar directo de preparar kilos y no
realize that the account was
me daba cuenta que la cuenta estaba
logged in, that's it, I'm like that but
iniciada sesión ya está soy así pero
well it wasn't bad at all or at all
bueno no era para nada malo ni para nada
boy okay it's not that it wasn't anything
chico vale no es que no era nada
related to salsa it was for one for a
relacionado con salsa era para una para
thing of mine coming one by one
un tema mío venir de uno en uno
no fear that is uncomfortable and
ningún miedo eso sí es incomodidad y
this is my first donation armando thank you
esta es mi primera donación armando
very much king that very well this
muchísimas gracias rey que muy bien este
is the gentleman I think he has guessed it very
es el señor creo que lo ha acertado muy
well I
bien
'm not worried I'm not afraid
no estoy preocupado no tengo miedo
of anyone and whoever wants to come can
ninguno de nadie y el que quiera venir
come but with their face uncovered because
que venga pero con la cara destapada que
here I hope to do it or none I
aquí lo espero realizar o ninguno
think it's a very clear message okay
yo creo que es un mensaje muy claro vale
a little indirect a little direct but
un poco indirecta un poco directa pero
for me the message has been very clear
para mí el mensaje ha sido muy claro
okay I think he put this video
vale yo creo que él ha puesto este vídeo
even though I had seen it because he
a pesar de que lo había visto porque lo
wanted to put it because it's entertaining
ha querido poner porque está entretenido
I don't believe much in these
yo no creo mucho en estas cosas del
tarot things what would I ask for in the future
tarot que pediría en el futuro
these things okay but I do like to have my
estas movidas vale pero sí que me gusta
cards read and that
mucho que me lean las cartas y que
mentally they have a mind they have a flame it's
mentalmente tienen mente tienen llama es
like I don't believe much but there's something in
como que no creo mucho pero hay algo de
me that says oh yes yes yes no  12 I think
mí que dice ay sí sí sí no 12 yo creo
that the video was posted apart from for
que el vídeo lo ha puesto aparte de por
entertainment to send that message
entretener pues para lanzar ese mensaje
that they can eat his games that they
de que le pueden comer los juegos de que
can come and eat his balls
le pueden venir y comer en los huevos
those who want to come and attack him with
los que quieran venir a atacarle con
things with certain things okay I think
cosas con ciertas cosas vale yo creo que
it's a bit of a message like saying come
es un poco mensajes como diciendo venir
with your face uncovered come and attack me
con la cara destapada venir y atacarme
but know that you're going to have to
pero que sepáis que se las vais a tener
deal with me I think that's
que ver conmigo yo creo que por ahí va
the message and well kid this is where
el mensaje y bueno chaval es hasta aquí
today's live ends I'm very exhausted it
el directo de hoy estoy muy agotado ha
was a very very very intense live don't
sido un directo muy muy muy intenso no
tell me you didn't appear live very very very
me digáis que no ha aparecido en directo
intense thank you very much
muy muy muy intenso muchísimas gracias
almost 26 thousand people renato rne
casi 26 mil personas renato rne
thank you very much welcome thank you very much almost 6000 people who have been here with me accompanying me I'm leaving now I'm going to rest and he's going to say yes tomorrow I'll direct the main channel but I think we can't on my sister's birthday and
podemos en el cumpleaños de mi hermana y
tomorrow I'm going to be disconnected okay
mañana voy a estar desconectado vale
these days taking advantage of the salsa it's
estos días aprovechando del salsero está
a little low well surely I'll be
un poco bajo pues seguramente estaré
taking a little rest too
tomándome un poco de descanso también
okay
vale
no not completely but I  I'll take it
no no del todo pero me lo tomaré con más
easy okay I could talk about things and there are
calma vale podría hablar de cosas y hay
things to get out to direct the video
que sacar cosas para director el vídeo
but I won't be as active as
pero no estaré tan activo como el mes
last month last month was December and I
pasado el mes pasado fue diciembre y
was here the boomer as if I didn't
estuve aquí el boomer como si no lo
know him and I don't whip him it's more that he
conociera y no lo fustiga es más que
has to put the tablet to charge in the
tiene que poner la tablet a cargar al
sun and it's winter well he'll do less and
sol y es invierno bueno hará menos y
play jokes on you or not but you're
gastarte bromas o no pero que me estás
paying me the 50 euros but you're
pagando los los 50 euros pero estás
paying me little by little how are you going to
pagando poco a poco como me lo vas a
pay me little by little
pagar poco a poco
because you feel guilty
porque te sientes con culpabilidad
well I don't buy from you just kidding just
pues a mí no se me compra es broma es
kidding because now he sent me an
broma de broma porque ahora me mandó un
audio that calm down okay obviously it's
audio que más calma vale evidentemente
not that I'm going to be inactive or anything but
no es que vaya estar inactivo ni mucho
hey if today I know how to
menos pero sí que oye si hoy me sé
get into being with the family I'm going to
meterse a estar con la familia voy a
be with the family if tomorrow I do
estar con la familia si mañana no sé
n't know how to get into not doing live I won't do it tomorrow I'm going to record a video in the main I'll record it I'm going to be more calm not as intensely as in December that December has been beastly it turned out very well in December okay it
ha salido muy bien en diciembre vale
was a lot of pain but it's time to
haber sido mucho la pena pero toca
rest a little at least the mind
descansar un poco por lo menos la mente
okay not completely but a little yes
vale no del todo pero un poco sí
but it has always been tremendous because
pero siempre ha sido tremendo porque
December has been almost every day
diciembre ha sido casi todos los días
possible making videos for the
posibles haciendo vídeo para el canal
main channel and every second has been non-
principal y el cada segundo ha sido no
stop, okay, so that's what January will do.
parar completo vale así que eso hará
I will be a little calmer but not
estaré un poquito más calmado pero no
inactive, don't confuse it, just a little
inactivo no confundáis solo un poco más
calmer. When there are topics that are really
calmado cuando haya temas que realmente
worth it, I will make videos directly.
merezcan la pena haré directo vídeos